<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>James Kettle on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in James Kettle on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>http://example.org/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 20:47:00 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/links/</guid>
      <description>Marginal Revolution Tyler Cowens Blog. One of the best on the internet. Topics: Economics, Current Events, Everything
Works In Progress &amp;ldquo;Works in Progress is an online magazine dedicated to sharing new and underrated ideas to improve the world&amp;rdquo; Great writing, always intresting topics.
Grewn Grewn. psychology, statistics, and technology. Legend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Website</title>
      <link>http://example.org/writing/simple_website/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 19:05:51 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/writing/simple_website/</guid>
      <description>If you take a look at this website, it is very simple. I made my personal website as simple and as fast as possible. I did this because I have noticed a pretty reliable trend where the more polished or attractive the homepage of someone is, the higher the chance that person is a grifter. I am not a grifter. I want my ideas and my work to be displayed simply so that someone can easily take away everything they could need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Georgian Sketchbook #1: Early Days</title>
      <link>http://example.org/writing/ags2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 17:45:53 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/writing/ags2/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s July 11. It&amp;rsquo;s a misty morning in Tbilisi. The weather is much cooler than it was for the past few days. Tbilisi in the summer can be unbearably hot. There&amp;rsquo;s a light rain and slight fog that gently drapes over mountains that surround the city.
Tbilisi is amazing. Tbilisi is chaotic. Tbilisi is hard to understand. I understand why I wanted to come here. For Westerners, the city feels mostly like a typical European city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Georgian Sketchbook #0: Before we fly.</title>
      <link>http://example.org/writing/ageorgiansketchbook0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 14:32:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/writing/ageorgiansketchbook0/</guid>
      <description>This is the first article of my series on my travels and interviews in Georgia.
There are times when places speak to you more than words. They speak a language that can&amp;rsquo;t be translated or understood by anyone else but you. Not everyone is lucky enough to have a place that speaks to them; some are so fortunate that they can have a conversation with every place they visit. I&amp;rsquo;m lucky that I found one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://example.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 17:34:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is James Kettle. I&amp;rsquo;m a writer and programmer currently living in Tbilisi, Georgia.
Background I went to Columbia and Sciences Po (‘23) and have two degrees, one in Economics and one in Information Science (a mix of Sociology and CS). I have worked at BlackRock, Plural Strategy Consulting, a school in France, and an NGO called Impact Jeunes in Marseille. After I graduated in May 2023, I decided to move to Georgia and become a math teacher at the Georgian American School.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
